flixify.com 2010-06-22

# Your privacy is something we take seriously, please read our policy

Flixify puts a lot of effort into keeping customer information secure. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our website and register to become a member. Please read this notice carefully.

### Personal Information

In order for you to join our community, we need your email address. We may also request your name, geographical location and telephone number to provide you additional services. Flixify does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. Flixify will never, and we repeat never, sell, rent or share your personal information, including your Email address, with any third parties for marketing purposes without your express permission. "Express permission" means you will know if you gave us permission because the permission check box will be big enough that you can actually read it. Flixify may share your personal information for the purpose of delivering Email to you or as required by law.

### Non-personal information

We may also ask non-personal identifiable information such as: annual income, buying preferences, or age. Also known as demographic and profile data, this information is optional. We will use this data to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site. We may also share this information with others in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

### Usage Information

Flixify may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers’ use of our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to among other things prepare for traffic load demands and to keep the site running smoothly.

### Review and Access

If you would like, we can provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You are welcome to correct, update or modify this information.

### Choice/Opt-Out

If we ever send you information by Email concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with a link to opt out of receiving such notices.

### Tracking

Like most sites, Flixify uses browser “cookies.” Cookies are small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. Flixify will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

### Links to Other Sites

As part of the service, Flixify may create links allowing you to access third party sites. Flixify is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not expressly endorse these sites. Please consult those sites’ privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

### Security

All the information described above is stored on restricted database servers, your information is safe with us.

### Modification to this Policy

Flixify can change this policy, but if we do we will post any changes here. If the changes are anything more than minor touchups on our legalese, we will send you a notice of what changed and why. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us at [support@flixify.com](mailto:support@flixify.com)

### Effective Date

This policy was last modified March 5, 2009
